Oh, what a lovely sound, Elisha.
Thank you.
Whoops.
Whoa, I guess I'm not that good at the steel drum.
But my son, Wes, is very good.
He's taking lessons from my wife on our homemade steel drum.
But the other day, Wes didn't want to play his drum.
He told us that another kid at school said his drum sounded funny.
Oh, no, that is awful.
Yeah, I know.
It bothered me.
And I could tell it really bothered Wes, too.
I just didn't know what to say.
I was upset.
I realized I needed to take a pause.
That is a great idea.
Sometimes we need to take a breather.
Yeah, I need to understand how I felt and acknowledge how Wes felt.
Then I reminded him that he plays the steel drums because it connects to his ancestors.
Oh, his Aunt Esther?
Oh, must be a wonderful woman.
No, no, no.
Ancestors, where and who we come from.
You see, Wes has African-American roots from me and Caribbean roots from his mom.
Her parents come from Trinidad, where the steel drum is played.
From Trinidad, you say?
Yep.
I reminded Wes of that.
I just needed a moment to gather myself.
See, you don't have to answer right away.
It's just important that you do answer.
Right, Grover?
No, I am pausing.
Remember, you do not have to answer right away.
You just said that.
Yeah, I did.